http://www.luctonians.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Welcome
Forgot password?
Not a member? Join today
http://www.luctonians.co.uk/wp-login.php?action=logout&redirect_to=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.luctonians.co.uk&_wpnonce=81a6c23a7c
Privacy Policy
Policy text last updated 18th May 2018.
Who we are
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Luctonians RFC collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of https://www.luctonians.co.uk. This privacy policy applies to the website and all products and services offered by Luctonians RFC.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Personal information is information about yourself that we need to be able to identify you. This information includes your name, your email address and sometimes your telephone number.
We may also collect information about your visits to our website, for example how you accessed our website, where you accessed our website from and what you searched for on our website.
For more information about the more technical information we may collect, such as the IP address (the location of the computer on the Internet) and cookies, please see our cookies section below.
If you are a registered user and upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with EXIF GPS location data included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
We use your personal data to:
Provide you with products/services you have requested from us;
To notify you about changes to our service;
To allow you to participate in interactive features on our website, when you choose to do so;
To improve our website to ensure that content is presented in the best way for you and your computer;
To help us with our work and activities so that we can make sure any advertising we send to you is relevant, if you have agreed to us sending you this;
For our own administrative operations, for example, for research and statistics;
To provide you with information about the goods and services we offer, if you have agreed to receive this information.
Contact forms
We use contact forms to collect personal information from you that we need to be able to identify you. This information allows us to provide you with products/services you have requested from us. This information may include your name, your email address and sometimes your telephone number.
We do not use the information submitted through contact forms for marketing purposes unless you have explicitly given us permission to do so.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the website we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Cookies
We use cookies on the website for our own internal purposes, to track how users navigate through the website. This helps us to evaluate and improve our website and our online services.
We use information derived from cookies in order to:
Compile statistics on how our website is being used, which can help us to improve our website and online services.
Facilitate users’ ability to navigate through the website.
Ascertain whether the website is operating effectively.
Personalise and improve the service we offer you by understanding your preferences and establishing which areas of the website are most relevant to you.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt in to saving your name, email address, and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Active Cookies
Name
Value
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use Google Analytics on our website in order to compile statistics on how our website is being used, which can help us to improve our website and online services. We anonymise all IP addresses gathered through this service so your IP address cannot be linked directly to your personal information.
Who we share your data with
We may have to share your personal information with other businesses and/or suppliers in order to provide you with products/services you have requested/ordered.
Where you have given us permission to contact you, we may pass on your information to external service providers to contact you on our behalf.
We may need to share your personal information with our search engine providers so they can assist with the improvement of our website.
If another party wants to invest in us or we are taken over by another party, we may need to share your personal information with them.
We may need to share your personal information for legal reasons.
How long we retain your data
Any contact form entries we receive are deleted after 6 months. Our analytics records are automatically deleted after 26 months, or when you request their deletion. We keep customer purchase records for 8 years.
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
The rights you have under data protection law are:
The right to access your personal information;
The right to amend your personal information;
The right to instruct us to delete your personal information;
The right to restrict how we use your personal information;
The right to object to us using your personal information;
The right to use the personal information we hold to transfer this to other services;
The right to complain to a supervisory authority if you think we are not using your personal information correctly; and
The right to withdraw consent for us to use your personal data.
You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal information by contacting us on  01568 709080 or by emailing cluboffice@luctonians.co.uk or you can write to us at our address: Mortimer Park, Hereford Rd, Kingsland, Leominster HR6 9SB
We will always ask for your permission to use your personal information for marketing purposes or prior to sharing this information with a third party for such purposes. You will be asked to tick certain boxes on the forms we use in order to opt in to us retaining your personal information and permit us to use your personal information in this way.
Our website may, from time to time, contain links to other websites. If you follow one of these links, please note that these websites will have their own Privacy Policies and that you will need to read these. Please make sure you read these policies before you submit any personal information to these websites.
You can request a copy of the personal information we hold about you at any time. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please let us know by contacting us on 01568 709080  or by sending an email to cluboffice@luctonians.co.uk or you can write to us at our address: Mortimer Park, Hereford Rd, Kingsland, Leominster HR6 9SB
If you have an account or have left comments on this website, you can request to receive an export file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we delete any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
The personal information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored, at a location outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or one of our suppliers. These staff may be involved in, among other things, the processing of your payment details, the provision of support services and the fulfillment of your order.
By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal information, we will use strict procedures and security features to prevent unauthorised access
In cases when we use external websites provided by other organisations such as Twitter, YouTube or Facebook, then we would ask you to consult their privacy policies.
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. This may be located abroad.
Our contact information
You can contact Luctonians RFC via the following methods:
Telephone: 01568 709080
Email: cluboffice@luctonians.co.uk
Postal Address: Mortimer Park, Hereford Rd, Kingsland, Leominster HR6 9SB
How we protect your data
We use an SSL certificate in order to encrypt any data sent between you and the server. All administrators of this website are required to use strong passwords and two factor authentication in order to minimise any risk of unauthorised entry.
What data breach procedures we have in place
In the case of a data breach we will inform the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) within 72 hours of the suspected breach. When we know information about a breach, we will provide this to individuals affected, together with advice to help them protect themselves from its effects.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
You have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) if you believe your personal information has been processed in a way that does not comply with the GDPR. You can do so by calling the ICO helpline on 0303 123 1113 or via their website https://ico.org.uk/.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkRead more
